I remember distinctly being told you got
to get the white girls to like you once
you get the white girls to like you the
sky's the limit like that was like an
actual like goal that that someone had
set for me I was like well damn
maybe they're right and so I started
doing that dance of trying to adjust
myself and like fit into this you know
kind of suit that had been made for me
by this I by this concept and then I
went and saw 12 Years a Slave and
literally when I saw 12 Years a Slave I
stepped outside the theater and you know
I said to myself you're gonna be as
black as you want to be and if there's a
space that doesn't allow you to do that
then it's not the space for you
[Music]